SHAUN WANG

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

+1 (929) 456 0753 shaunzwang@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/shaun-z-wang/ https://github.com/shaun86wang

SUMMARY

Passionate software engineer with industry software development experience, comprehensive academic education, and knowledge of various types of technologies. Distinct ability to learn things fast while dedicated to providing high-quality results both at work and school. Highly motivated and diligent self-learner. Responsible leader and proactive communicator with strong interpersonal skills.

EDUCATION

Grand Canyon University, Phoenix, AZ

| Graduating 04/2019 |

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science with an Emphasis in Big Data Analytics

3.99 Cumulative GPA

Member of Alpha Chi National College Honor Society

Recipient of GCU Honors College Inspiring Leader Award

Recipient of GCU Highest Tier of Scholarship

GCU Honors College Leadership and Career Training Program 2nd Place Holder

Member of Smart Urban Fabrics Research Design Program

SKILLS

LANGUAGES | C# | Java | JavaScript | TypeScript | JSX | HTML | CSS | Python | R | SQL |

| C++ | Matlab | MIPS Assembly |

FRAMEWORK | .NET | Spring | Angular | React | JQuery | Bootstrap |

TOOLS | Visual Studio | Spring Tool Suite | CLion | PyCharm | Unity | SQL Server | Git |

| Azure DevOps | JUnit | Maven |

SDLC | Scrum | Kanban | Continuous Delivery | QA |

KNOWLEDGE | Data Structures | Algorithms | OOP | MVC | REST API | Design Patterns |

Computer Architecture | Machine Learning | Web Security | Operating Systems |

| Statistics | Multivariable Calculus | Linear Algebra | Accessibility |

EXPERIENCE

Junior Web Developer (Part-time)

| 03/2016 - PRESENT |

Grand Canyon University, Phoenix, AZ

- Participate in full stack web development in a scrum team utilizing Angular, .NET, .NET Core, C#, SQL, Visual Studio, Azure, etc, to add features to business applications.
- Maintain and refactor existing web applications, one of which saved GCU over \$2,000,000 in 2017.

Software Engineer Intern

| 06/2018 - 08/2018 |

Albertsons Companies, Phoenix, AZ

- Developed ServiceNow platform by writing Business Rules, Client Scripts, UI Script, Script Includes, Background Scripts, Scheduled Jobs, Condition Scripts.
- Integrated ServiceNow with third-party platforms by creating REST APIs.
- Created Service Portal for third-party vendors using Widgets, AngularJS, and JS Include.

Web Queueing System

| 08/2018 - PRESENT |

- Create an online queuing system for GCU mail center that allows students to get in line remotely.
- Use Spring Boot as the backend, React as the frontend, REST API and WebSocket for data transfer, MySQL database, Azure for continuous delivery and hosting, and SendGrid for email service.

Machine Learning Web Application

| 08/2018 - PRESENT |

- Build a web app for text classification and image detection using machine learning algorithms in R
- Demo: http://shaunwang.shinyapps.io/R_Machine_Learning/

Physics Lab Simulation Project Using Microsoft HoloLens

| 08/2017 - 01/2018 |

- Used Unity and C# to create a mixed reality application running on MS HoloLens to offer an innovative methodology for conducting an academic physics lab.
- Demo: http://bit.ly/smurfhololens

LEADERSHIP